gunsamerica.com 2000-12-06

# 

GunsAmerica Sellers: $1,000 Cash for Guns!! Click Here to enter our Jan. 1 2001 drawing.  
Privacy Statement for GunsAmerica

## Privacy Statement for GunsAmerica

[](http://www.truste.org/) GunsAmerica LLC has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website: GunsAmerica.

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. Your IP address is used to gather broad demographic information for server hit statistics. We use cookies to save your password so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit our site.

Our site's registration form (New Sellers) requires users to give us contact information (like their name, address, phone and email address). For WishList registration we only require a valid email address. In addition, on the New Sellers form, there is a checkbox to hide your address from visitors. **GunsAmerica does not share your private information with anyone.**

The customer's contact information is used to contact the visitor when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. 

This site contains links to other sites. **GunsAmerica** is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites, however we do not in any way share your contact information with them. 

## Public Forums

This site makes a public Guestbook available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.

## Choice/Opt-Out

Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us. 

  1. You can send email to [support@gunsamerica.com](mailto:support@gunsamerica.com)
  2. You can call the following telephone number: 603.595.9253

## Change/Modify

GunsAmerica also gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided, or for checking the "hide my address box" after registering. 

  1. visit Your Account at:<http://www.gunsamerica.com/addguns.cgi>

## Contacting the Web Site

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact Shlomo Helinski Customer Support Representative GunsAmerica LLC 142 Main Street Suite 217 Morristown, NJ 07960 privacy@gunsamerica.com

If you haven't registered as a seller yet, Click Here to sell your guns on GunsAmerica right now! 

* * *

Content, Design, Coding, © Copyright 1997, 1998, GunsAmerica  
Some Trademarks are the property of their respective title holders.  
GunsAmerica LLC  
GunsAmerica Payments  
P.O. Box 1793  
Morristown, NJ 07960
